Finding Aid for David W. Osler papers, 1956-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Architectural Drawings
  - Conlin, William J., Building Additions and Alterations, Huron Street, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1962)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 2/16/1962-3/31/1962; 9 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 2, Folder 2)
  - Corwin, Mr. & Mrs. Frederic W., Residence, Conifer Knolls, Jackson, Michigan (1967)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 11/15/1967; 15 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 1, Folder 8)
  - Crooked Tree District Library, North Shore Drive, Walloon Lake, Michigan (1998-1999)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler Associates, Inc., Architects, and North Star Land Surveying, 10/20/1998-8/22/1999; 33 drawings architectural surveys, mechanical drawings (building systems drawings), electrical drawings; pencil drawings on vellum and paper and CAD drawings on vellum and mylar (Map-case 2, Folder 3)
  - David W. Osler, Architect, Office Addition and Alterations, 916 Fuller Street, Ann Arbor, Michigan (2008)
    - Design Development and Construction Drawings, one dated, 6/26/2008; 15 drawings architectural sketches and drawings; ink and pencil drawings on tracing paper, blue-line print and vellum (Map-case 2, Folder 2)
  - Dawn Farm Buildings, Stony Creek Road Ypsilanti, Michigan (1986)
    - Perspective Drawings by David W. Osler, Osler/Milling Architects, Inc., undated; 5 drawings pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 2, Folder 4)
    - Site Survey by Washtenaw Engineering Co., Inc., 10/31/1986; 1 drawings blue-line print (Map-case 2, Folder 4)
    - Design Development Drawings by Osler Milling Architects, Inc., undated; 7 drawings architectural drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 2, Folder 4)
  - Dobson, Jack, Residence, Barton Hills, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1956)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 3/26/1956; 17 drawings architectural and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 2, Folder 4)
  - Emmanuel Lutheran Church, Livonia, Michigan (1991)
    - Perspective Drawing by David W. Osler Associates, Inc., Architects, 9/24/1991; 1 drawings pencil-on-vellum original (Map-case 1, Folder 3)
  - Fife Electric Company Office and Warehouse, Novi, Michigan
    - Perspective Drawing by David W. Osler, undated; 1 drawings pencil-on-vellum original (Map-case 1, Folder 3)
  - Ford, Mr. & Mrs. James W., Residence, Riverview Drive, Ann Arbor, MI (1968)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 5/3/1968; 14 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil drawings on vellum and on sepia prints (Map-case 2, Folder 5)
  - Fosdick, Mr. & Mrs. Dale, Residence, Hunting Valley Road and Provincial Drive, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1963)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 3/1/1963; 15 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 2, Folder 5)
  - Freeman, Frederick W. & Nancy P., Residence, Willow Lane, Birmingham, Michigan (1989)
    - Construction Drawings by Osler Milling Architects, Inc., 9/15/1989; 11 drawings architectural drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 2, Folder 6)
  - Gallup Park Livery Building, Ann Arbor Department of Parks and Recreation, Huron Parkway and Fuller Road, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1984-1985)
    - Construction Drawings by Osler Milling Architects, Inc., 1/3/1984; 9/18/1985; 21 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical;plumbing drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals and one sepia print (Map-case 2, Folder 6)
  - Gilkey, Dr. & Mrs. William C., Residence, Windemere Lake, Adrian, Michigan (1964)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect 1/3/1964 revised 3/27/1964, 19 drawings architectural, structural and mechanical;electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 2, Folder 7)
  - Greene, Mr. & Mrs. Paul, Residence, Oakdale Road, Barton Hills, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1967-1969)
    - Design Development and Construction Drawing by David W. Osler, Architect, 9/20/1967-2/21/1969; 23 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 2, Folder 8)
  - Grosse Pointe Public Library Main Branch Addition, Grosse Pointe Farms, Michigan (ca. 1990)
    - Preliminary Drawings by Osler/Milling Architects, Inc., and George Jerome & Co., Surveyors, survey dated, 2/16/1990; 3 drawings perspective drawings; 1 drawings site plan; pencil-on-vellum originals and colored pencil drawing on sepia print (Map-case 1, Folder 3)
  - Hakken, Mr. & Mrs. Howard, Residence Renovation, Hill Avenue, Grand Rapids, Michigan (1983)
    - Construction Drawings by Osler/Milling Architects, Inc., undated; 14 drawings architectural and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 2, Folder 7)
  - Harry S. Peterson Co., Inc., Office and Storage Facility and Office Building Addition, Orion Township, Michigan (1985-1988) (Map-case 2, Folder 7)
  - Henrie, Arthur & Sally, Residence, Skiff Lake, Jackson, Michigan (1981-1988) (Map-case 2, Folder 9)
    - Design Development Drawings, five dated, 1/1981-11/20/1988; 15 drawings architectural surveys and architectural drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 2, Folder 10)
    - Construction Drawings by Osler/Milling Architects, Inc., 5/25/1981-10/7/1981; 22 drawings architectural, structural and mechanical;electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 2, Folder 10)
  - Hodges, Maurice B., Residence, East Shore Drive, Whitmore Lake, Michigan (1970-1971)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 12/30/1970-1/15/1971; 9 drawings architectural and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 2, Folder 8)
  - Hoffman Building, Plymouth Road Development, Ann Arbor, Michigan, undated
    - Perspective Drawing by David W. Osler, 1 drawings pencil-on-vellum original (Map-case 1, Folder 3)
  - Howell Carnegie District Library Restoration and Expansion, West Grand River Avenue, Howell, Michigan (1988-1990)
    - Existing Building Construction Drawings by Osler Milling Architects, Inc., Boss Engineering, John Grissim and Associates, Inc., Site Planners, and Quinn Evans, Architects (Map-case 2, Folder 11)
      - Landscape Drawings, 5/27/1988-10/19/1989; 9 drawings demolition surveys, grading plans, utility plans, irrigaiion drawings; pencil notations on mylar prints (Map-case 2, Folder 11)
      - Architectural Drawings (A-1 to A-24) 6/12/1989 revised 9/22/1989, 25 drawings pencil drawings on blue-line prints and vellum (Map-case 2, Folder 12)
    - Expansion Building Construction Drawings by Osler Milling Architects, Inc. (Map-case 3, Folder 1)
      - Architectural Drawings (A-30 to A-45) 6/12/1989 revised 9/22/1989 one dated 3/2/1990, 18 drawings pencil notations on mylar prints (Map-case 3, Folder 1)
      - Architectural Drawings (A-46 to A-64) 6/12/1989 revised 9/22/1989, 16 drawings pencil notations on mylar prints (Map-case 3, Folder 2)
      - Structural and Electrical Drawings of Existing and Expansion Buildings by Osler Milling Architects, Inc., Robert Darvas Associates, P.C., Structural Engineers, BADA Engineering and Quinn Evans, Architects 6/12/1989 revised 6/18/1990, 14 drawings pencil notations on mylar prints (Map-case 3, Folder 3)
  - Independence Lake Park Pavilion, Washtenaw County, Michigan (1978-1987)
    - Independence Park I (Map-case 3, Folder 4)
      - Preliminary Drawings by David W. Osler, undated; 4 drawings perspectives; 1 drawings site plan; pencil-on-vellum drawings (Map-case 3, Folder 4)
      - Preliminary Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect 11/6/1978 revised 6/11/1979, 3 drawings architectural drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 4)
    - Independence Park II
      - Construction Drawings by Osler Milling Architects, Inc. 8/3/1987 revised 8/31/1987, 6 drawings architectural drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 4)
  - Jacobusse, Mr. & Mrs. K. D., Cottage, Lone Pine Road, Bloomfield Hills, Michigan (1973)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 4/27/1973; 9 drawings architectural and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 4)
  - Jones, Mr. & Mrs. L. W., Residence, Huron River Heights, Scio Township, Michigan (1967)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 5/1/1967; 14 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 5)
  - Kahler, Dr. & Mrs. F. W., Jr., Residence, Glendaloch Road, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1965-1966)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, and Charles W. Cares, Landscape Architect, 12/20/1965-1/3/1966; 19 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical;landscape drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 5)
  - Kalamazoo/Arcadia Creek Urban Design & Development Plan, Kalamazoo, Michigan
    - Preliminary Drawings by The Osler/Milling/Wang Partnership and Charles W. Moore, FAIA; Melvin F. Levine & Associates, Inc./Urban Development Consultant; and Besier Gibble & Quirin/Consulting Engineers
      - Presentation Board I, undated; 1 drawings site plan; ink and colored pencil drawing on poster board (Map-case 6, Folder 8)
      - Presentation Board II, undated; 1 drawings site plan; ink and colored pencil drawing on poster board (Map-case 6, Folder 9)
      - Presentation Board III, undated; 6 drawings perspectives; water-color paintings on poster board (Map-case 6, Folder 10)
      - Presentation Board IV, undated; 6 drawings perspectives; water-color paintings on poster board (Map-case 6, Folder 11)
  - Kirshner Residence, Buno Road, Milford Township, Michigan (1993)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler Associates, Inc., Architects, 4/14/1993-10/13/1993; 16 drawings architectural, structural and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals and mylar prints (Map-case 3, Folder 6)
  - Koeze, Mary Beth, Residence, Grass Lake Road, Washtenaw County, Michigan (1995)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler Associates, Inc., Architects, 6/20/1995; 10 drawings architectural drawings; pencil drawings on mylar prints (Map-case 3, Folder 6)
  - Kumasaka, Mr. & Mrs. Glen H., Residence, Enclave Drive, Ann Arbor Township, Michigan (1969)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 10/16/1969; 15 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 7)
  - Kumasaka, Mr. & Mrs. Glen H., Residence Additions and Alterations, Cedar Bend Drive, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1970-1971 & 1986)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 7/21/1970-5/24/1971; 22 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 7)
    - Construction Drawings of Master Bedroom Addition by Osler Milling Architects, Inc., 7/2/1986; 3 drawings architectural drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 7)
  - Lakelands Country Club
    - Perspective Drawing by David W. Osler, undated; 1 drawings pencil-on-vellum original (Map-case 3, Folder 8)
      (1 drawing of 2 elevations)
  - Lansing, J. B., Cabin (1963)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 4/23/1963; 5 drawings architectural drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 9)
  - Lee, N. W., Cottage and Additions/Alterations, Lakeshore Drive, Holland, Michigan (1977)
    - Design Development and Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 1/21/1977; 14 drawings perspectives and architectural;electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 9)
  - Leslie Park Golf Course Starting House, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1968)
    - Perspective Drawing by David W. Osler, undated; 1 drawings pencil-on-vellum original (Map-case 3, Folder 10)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, and Migdal, Layne & Sachs, Inc., Consulting Engineers, 3/22/1968; 12 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 10)
  - Madison Square Condominiums (2006)
    - Design Development Drawings, two dated, 3/8/2006; 11 drawings perspectives, sketches and architectural drawings; pencil and ink drawings on tracing paper, vellum and blue-line prints and one electrostatic print (Map-case 3, Folder 10)
  - Malcolm, Dr. & Mrs. Karl Residence, Barton Hills, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1967)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 2/3/1967; 17 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 11)
  - Marcus Cottage, Walloon Lake, Michigan (1985)
    - Construction Drawings by Osler Milling Architects, Inc., 3/22/1985-6/25/1985; 11 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 11)
  - McFadden Residence, Lakeshore Drive, Holland, Michigan (1977)
    - Design Development and Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 9/12/1977-11/15/1977; 13 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 12)
  - Medical Data Systems Building Faade, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1978)
    - Perspective Drawing by David W. Osler, 1978; 1 drawings pencil-on-vellum original (Map-case 3, Folder 8)
  - Mount Pleasant Conference Center Creamery Rehabilitation, Mount Pleasant, Michigan (1982)
    - Perspective Drawings by David W. Osler, undated; 2 drawings pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 8)
  - Mundus, Mr. & Mrs. William J., Residence, Highland Terrace, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1963)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 9/1/1963; 15 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 13)
  - Mundus, Mr. & Mrs. William, Residence, Regent Drive, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1977)
    - Perspective Drawings by David W. Osler, 1977; 2 drawings pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 13)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 8/26/1977; 14 drawings architectural and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 3, Folder 13)
  - National Bank and Trust Company of Ann Arbor Renovation, Main and Washington Streets, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1974-1980)
    - Construction Drawings of Exterior by David W. Osler, Architect, 12/31/1974-1/23/1975; 1 drawings perspective; 7 drawings architectural, structural and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 4, Folder 1)
    - Design Development and Construction Drawings of Interior by David W. Osler, Architect, 6/7/1974-1/10/1978; 25 drawings perspectives and architectural;electrical drawings; pencil drawings on vellum and tracing paper (Map-case 4, Folder 1)
    - Construction Drawings by Osler Milling Architects, Inc., 10/8/1979-4/18/1980; 5 drawings architectural and furniture layout drawings; pencil drawings on vellum and tracing paper (Map-case 4, Folder 1)
  - Nellie S. Loving Branch Library and Addition, Creek Drive, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1963-1965 and 1978)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect 7/3/1963 revised 10/4/1965, 1 drawings perspective; 13 drawings architectural, structural and mechanical;electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 4, Folder 2)
    - Construction Drawings of Addition by David W. Osler & Partners, Inc., Architects, 10/31/1978; 11 drawings architectural, structural and mechanical;electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 4, Folder 2)
  - Newport West, Overlook Court, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1971-1979)
    - Preliminary Schemes by David W. Osler, Architect, Johnson, Johnson & Roy, Inc., Landscape Architects, and Norman L. Dietrich Associates, Site Engineers, 1971-1972; 2 drawings perspectives; 52 drawings surveys and architectural drawings; pencil originals on vellum and tracing paper and blue-line, sepia and mylar prints (Map-case 4, Folder 3)
    - Construction Drawings of Model Phase by David W. Osler, Architect, 10/4/1971-11/17/1971; 35 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical;plumbing drawings; pencil drawings on vellum and on mylar and sepia prints (Map-case 4, Folder 4)
    - Construction Drawings by David Osler, Architect, and David W. Osler & Partners, Inc. 11/17/1971 revised 1/3/1972 some revised 8/25/1978, 37 drawings architectural and mechanical drawings; pencil drawings on vellum and on sepia prints (Map-case 4, Folder 5)
    - Construction Drawings, Phase I, Reissued for Bid, by David W. Osler & Partners, Inc., and Osler/Milling Architects 11/17/1971 re-issued 8/25/1978 revised 1/17/1979, 39 drawings architectural and mechanical drawings; pencil drawings on vellum and on sepia prints (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
  - Orchard Professional Building, Plymouth Road, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1983-1984)
    - Construction Drawings by Osler/Milling Architects, Inc., Furstenburg, Crompton & Associates, Inc., Mechanical Engineer, and Neil Adams, Inc., Electrical Engineer, 10/31/1983-2/14/1984; 15 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals and mylar prints (Map-case 3, Folder 12)
  - Oshtemo Limited Dividend Housing Association, Evergreen North, Oshtemo Township, Michigan (1978)
    - Perspective Drawing by David W. Osler, 1978; 1 drawings pencil-on-vellum original (Map-case 3, Folder 8)
  - Osler, Mr. & Mrs. David W., Residence, Glazier Way, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1960)
    - Construction Drawing by David W. Osler, Architect, 2/15/1960; 17 drawings architectural drawings; pencil drawings on vellum and mylar (Map-case 3, Folder 14)
  - Oslund Condominiums, Glazier Way & Huron Parkway, Ann Arbor Michigan (1968-2003)
    - Preliminary Schemes (Map-case 4, Folder 7)
      - First Oslund Scheme Drawings after Oxford Original by David W. Osler, Architect, 3/20/1968; 37 drawings architectural, mechanical and landscape drawings; pencil drawings on vellum and on sepia prints (Map-case 4, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous Drawings, undated; 6 drawings perspectives and architectural drawings; ink drawings on mylar and on vellum (Map-case 4, Folder 7)
      - Preliminary Schemes Drawings, Oslund I & II, two drawings dated, 1973; 1977; 38 drawings perspectives, architectural drawings and sketches; pencil and ink drawings on vellum, tracing paper, sepia prints and blue-line prints (Map-case 4, Folder 8)
      - Oslund I Drawings Leading to Final Scheme # 4 by David W. Osler, Architect, one drawing dated, 3/30/1976; 13 drawings architectural drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 4, Folder 9)
      - Preliminary Scheme Drawings, Oslund III by David W. Osler, Architect, two drawings dated, 1974; 31 drawings architectural and perspective drawings;sketches; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 4, Folder 10)
    - Oslund I Drawings (Map-case 4, Folder 11)
      - Master Plan Documents by Atwell-Hicks, Civil Engineers, Surveyors, Planners, 7/20/1987; 10 drawings architectural surveys, landscape surveys, utility plans; mylar prints (Map-case 4, Folder 11)
      - Schematic Design Drawings, 6/3/1985-7/20/1987; 32 drawings architectural surveys, site plans, utility plans; plumbing drawings, landscape drawings; ink and pencil-on-vellum originals and sepia and blue-line prints (Map-case 4, Folder 12)
      - Construction Drawings by Osler/Milling Architects, Inc., 10/14/1985-4/16/1987; 31 drawings engineering, architectural and mechanical, electrical;plumbing drawings; mylar prints and pencil and ink originals on vellum and on sepia and blue-line prints (Map-case 4, Folder 13)
    - Oslund II Drawings (Map-case 5, Folder 1)
      - Site Plan Approval Documents by David W. Osler Associates, Inc., Architects, and Midwestern Consulting, LLC, 11/1/2000; 13 drawings site plans, utility plans, and architectural drawings; vellum and mylar prints (Map-case 5, Folder 1)
      - Third Amendment to Master Deed Documents by Midwestern Consulting, LLC, 6/21/2001; 8 drawings site plans, utility plans; architectural drawings; mylar prints (Map-case 5, Folder 1)
      - Oslund II, Inc., Construction Drawings by David W. Osler Associates, Inc., Architects, and Midwestern Consulting, LLC, 7/30/2001; 32 drawings architectural surveys, utility plans, stractural drawings, mechanical drawings (building systems drawings), electrical drawings; vellum and mylar prints (Map-case 5, Folder 2)
    - Oslund II & III Drawings (Map-case 5, Folder 3)
      - Fourth Amendment to Master Deed Documents by Midwestern Consulting, LLC, and Atwell-Hicks, Inc., 9/30/2003; 26 drawings site plans, utility plans, architectural drawings; vellum prints (Map-case 5, Folder 3)
      - Oslund III, Inc., Construction Drawings by David W. Osler Associates, Inc., Architects, and Midwestern Consulting, LLC, 7/30/2001-12/18/2003; 25 drawings architectural drawings and utility plans; CAD prints (Map-case 5, Folder 4)
      - Oslund III, Inc., Construction Drawings (cont.) by David W. Osler Associates, Inc., Architects, and Midwestern Consulting, LLC, 7/30/2001-12/18/2003; 25 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical;plumbing drawings; CAD prints (Map-case 5, Folder 5)
  - Papsdorf, James D. & Carol Mills, Residence, Gallagher Road, Strawberry Lake, Michigan (1975)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 8/1/1975; 14 drawings architectural and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 5, Folder 6)
  - Portland District Library, Kent Street, Portland, Michigan (2000-2004)
    - Schematic Design, Design Development and Construction Drawings by David W. Osler Associates, Inc., Mulder & Associates and HH Engineering, Limited, 12/28/2000-3/12/2004; 50 drawings perspective views (images) and architectural drawings; pencil drawings on tracing paper, vellum and blue-line prints and CAD drawings on paper (Map-case 5, Folder 7)
  - Pryor, Dr. & Mrs. David B., and Miner, Dr. & Mrs. James B., Residences, Portage Lake, Pinckey, Michigan (1973-1975)
    - Preliminary Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 5/18/1973-6/6/1973; 1 drawings perspective; 5 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 5, Folder 8)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 6/4/1973-8/27/1975; 8 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 5, Folder 8)
  - Pryor Cottage Addition, Portage Lake, Pinckey, Michigan (1979)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler & Partners, Inc., 2/5/1979-3/5/1979; 7 drawings architectural, structural and mechanical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 5, Folder 8)
  - Rapp, Dr. & Mrs. Robert, Residence Alterations, Cedar Bend Drive, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1966-1975)
    - Design Development and Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect &, 7/5/1966; 8/14/1975; 21 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 5, Folder 6)
  - Ratliff-Olson Residence, Glazier Way, Ann Arbor, Michigan (undated)
    - Design Development and Construction Drawings by David W. Osler Associates, Inc., undated; 19 drawings architectural and electrical drawings; original pencil and ink drawings on vellum and on one blue-line print (Map-case 5, Folder 9)
  - Ross, Professor & Mrs. Gilbert, Residence, Highland Lane, Ann Arbor, Michigan (1966-1990)
    - Construction Drawings by David W. Osler, Architect, 9/30/1965-7/18/1966; 15 drawings architectural, mechanical and electrical drawings; pencil-on-vellum originals (Map-case 5, Folder 9)
    - Glazing Replacement Details by David W. Osler Associates, Architects, Inc., 3/14/1990; 1 drawings architectural drawing; pencil-on-vellum original (Map-case 5, Folder 9)
  - Sandall, Dr. Gary, Residence (1978)